Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Espoir Place of publication: Toulouse, France Publisher: Unions Regionales de la C.N.T.F., 1973-1982 (Box 27)
- Fag Rag Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Fag Rag Inc., undated (Box 165)
- Fatigue Press Place of publication: Austin, Tex. Publisher: Ft. Hood GI's, 1969-1971 (Box 162)
- Fed Up! Place of publication: Tacoma, Wash., 1970-1973 (Box 162)
- The Federation Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York State AFL-CIO, 1978-1983 (Box 134)
- Federation Voice Place of publication: Maumee, Ohio Publisher: Federation of Long Lines Telephone Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 134)
- FedNews Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: National Association of Government Employees, 1982-2001 (Box 135)
- Feminist Art Journal Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Feminist Art Journal, Inc., 1972-1977 (Box 135)
- Feminist Bulletin Place of publication: Scarborough, N.Y. Publisher: Feminist Bulletin, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 130)
- Feminist Communications Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: Feminist Communications, 1978 (Box 134)
- Festival informa Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: XI Festival Mundial de la Juventud y los Estudiantes, Comisión Permanente del Comité Internacional Preparatorio, 1978 (Box 136)
- Fifth Estate Place of publication: Detroit, Mich., 1976-2000 (Box 135-136)
- Fight Against War and Fascism Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American League Against War and Fascism, 1933-1939 (Box 137-138)
- Fight for Peace and Democracy Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Executive Committee of the American League Against War and Fascism, 1938-1939 (Box 138)
- For the People Place of publication: New Bedford, Mass., 1977-1981 (Box 130)
- The Fourth International Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Organization of Executive Committee of Fourth International, 1968-1969 (Box 151)
- Fragging Action Place of publication: Cookeytown, N.J. Publisher: GI's of Fort Dix, 1971-1972 (Box 162)
- Free Labour World Place of publication: Belgium Publisher: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1985-1997 (Box 151)
- Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Free People's Movement, 2007-2007 (Box 162)
- Free Ranger Intertribal News Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Free Ranger Tribe and Underground Press Syndicate, 1970-1971 (Box 152)
- Freedom Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga., 1963-1964 (Box 152)
- Freedom Reader Place of publication: Flint, Mich. Publisher: Freedom Reader Publications, 1971-1971 (Box 157)
- Frontline Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Line of March Publications, 1972-1990 (Box 159-160)
- Frontpage Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, American Newspaper Guild, CIO, 1947-2000 (Box 173)
- Futuro Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: La Delegacion Del FORDC de Nueva York, 1962 (Box 28)
- La Gaceta de Cuba Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Grass Roots: National Newsletter of the People's Party, 1965 (Box 165)
- The Garden Place of publication: Binghamton, N.Y., 1988 (Box 165)
- The Garment Worker Place of publication: England Publisher: National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1976 (Box 165)
- The Gay Liberator Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Pansy Press, undated (Box 165)
- Gay Sunshine Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Winston Leyland, 1972-1976 (Box 165)
- Georgia Straight Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Georgia Straight Pub., 1971-1973 (Box 166)
- German American Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: German American Inc., 1942-1968 (Box 167-168)
- GI News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: NOSCAM-Chicago, 1974-1975 (Box 163)
- GI Press Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1970-1971 (Box 163)
- Gold Flower Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: The Gold Flower Collective, 1971-1979 (Box 477)
- Goodbye to All That Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1970-1971 (Box 171)
- The Government Standard Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
- Granpa Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1967-1968 (Box 171)
- Grapes of Wrath Place of publication: Norfolk, Va. Publisher: The Defense Committee-Tidewater, 1972-1975 (Box 163)
- Graphic Communicator Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Graphic Communications Union, 1983-2013 (Box 172-173)
- Grass Roots: National Newsletter of the People’s Party Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: People's Party, 1972-1975 (Box 174)
- Grass Roots Forum Place of publication: San Gabriel, Calif. Publisher: Grass Roots Publishing Co., 1972-1980 (Box 175)
- Great Speckled Bird Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Atlanta Cooperative News Project, 1971-1974 (Box 176)
- Green Politics Place of publication: Kansas City, Mo. Publisher: Greens/Green Party USA, 1992-1997 (Box 178)
- Green Revolution, 1972-1981 (Box 123)
- The Green Revolution Place of publication: Freeland, Md. Publisher: The School of Living, 1967-1981 (Box 123)
- Guardian Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Weekly Guardian Associates, 1968-1990 (Box 435)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7058)
- Guild Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1956-1960 (Box 66)
- Guild Bulletin / New York Teachers Guild Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1941-1947 (Box 65)
- Guild Notes Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, 1972-1988 (Box 177)
- Guild Reporter Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Newspaper Guild and Communications Reporter, 1994-2013 (Box 176A-176B)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7066)
- Guild Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1936-1942 (Box 65)
- Hard Times Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, University of Chicago Chapter, 1975-1976 (Box 179)
- Hard Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hard Times Conference, 1976 (Box 178)
- Harlem News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Architects' Renewal Committee in Harlem, 1971 (Box 38)
- Harrisburg Independent Press Place of publication: Harrisburg, Pa. Publisher: Harrisburg Independent Press, Inc., 1972 (Box 179)
- Health Rights News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1968-1972 (Box 178)
- Healthwire Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Federation of Teachers, 1981 (Box 488)
- 'Heights and 'Valley News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Columbia Tenants Union, 1973-1978 (Box 178)
- Hell on Wheels / By and For the Rank and File of TWU Local 100 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rank and File Movement in Local 100, 1984-2001 (Box 179)
- The Helping Hand Place of publication: Mountain Home, Idaho, 1972-1973 (Box 163)
- Hera Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Hera, Inc., 1975-1975 (Box 477)
- Hollywood Free Paper Place of publication: Hollywood, Calif. Publisher: Jesus People International, undated (Box 183)
- Homefront Place of publication: Dallas, Tex., undated (Box 181)
- The Hot Seat / Taxi Rank and File Coalition Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Taxi Rank and File Coalition, 1971-1977 (Box 183)
- Hotel/Restaurant Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, AFL-CIO and Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant, Club Employees and Bartenders Union, 1979-1983 (Box 181)
- Houston Breakthrough Place of publication: Houston, Tex. Publisher: Breakthrough Publishing Co., 1976-1979 (Box 163)
- Iconoclast Place of publication: Surrey, England Publisher: Millar, J.A., 1971 (Box 184)
- In These Times Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: New Majority Pub. Co., 1976-1991 (Box 185A-188)
- In Transit: Official Journal / Amalgamated Transit Union Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Amalgamated Transit Union, 1967-1988 (Box 192-193)
- The Incredible Bureaucrat Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969 (Box 189)
- Individuo nella società Place of publication: Italy, 1979-1980 (Box 189)
- Industrial Worker Place of publication: Ypsilanti, Mich. Publisher: Industrial Workers of the World, 1994-2013 (Box 205A)
- Indypendent: The Newspaper of NYC-IMC Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York City Independent Media Center, 2000-2013 (Box 190)
- Infusion: Tools for Action and Education Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Center for Campus Organizing, 1998-1999 (Box 111)
- Inner City Voice Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: League of Revolutionary Black Workers, 1967-1971 (Box 201)
- The Insurgent Place of publication: Eugene, Or. Publisher: The Insurgent, 2000-2001 (Box 201)
- Insurrection Place of publication: Paterson, N.J., undated (Box 201)
- Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center Bulletin Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center, 1986 (Box 191)
- International Musician: Official Journal of the American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada, 1997-2013 (Box 203A-203D)
- International Operating Engineer Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Union of Operating Engineers, 1998-2005 (Box 85)
- International Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Worker's Party, 1974-1976 (Box 205)
- Internationale Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Alliance Marxiste Révolutionnaire, 1970-1970 (Box 205)
- Internationalist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Mundial Publications, 1997-2014 (Box 218)
- Internationalist Worker Place of publication: New Haven, Boston, New York Conn., Mass., N.Y. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist League, 1974-1979 (Box 205)
- Issue Place of publication: Columbia, Mo. Publisher: Ideographics INC., 1971 (Box 206)
- IUSY Survey Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: International Union of Socialist Youth, 1952-1968 (Box 184)
- Jewish Liberation Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Jewish Liberation Project, 1969-1972 (Box 208)
- The Jewish Radical Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Union of Jewish Students, 1969-1972 (Box 208)
- Journal Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen, 1982-1988 (Box 208)
- Jump Cut Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Jump Cut Associates, 1974-1986 (Box 208A)
- Ka Huliau Place of publication: Honolulu, Hawaii Publisher: Hawaii Education for Social Progress, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 213)
- Keep Left Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Young Socialists, 1961-1971 (Box 497)
- Kent Dragonfire Place of publication: Kent, Ohio Publisher: Y.I.P., 1971-1971 (Box 213)
- Kick It Over Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Kick It Over Collective, 1983-1990 (Box 213)
- Krokodil Place of publication: Moscow, U.S.S.R. Publisher: Izd. Gazety "Pravda", 1930-1959 (Box 213)
- Kultur Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1925-1926 (Box 214A)
- Labor Action Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Labor Action Coalition, 2004-2004 (Box 220)
- Labor Militant Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Labor Militant Collective, 1986-1990 (Box 215)
- Labor News Place of publication: Rochester, N.Y. Publisher: Central Trades and Labor Council, 2004-2007 (Box 216A)
- Labor Today Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Association for Economic Studies, 1971-1987 (Box 219A)
- Labor Unity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, 1982-1995 (Box 221-222)
- Lavender Vision Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Media Collective, undated (Box 165)
- Leviathan Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: V.R. Leviathan Publications, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 219, Box Shared Tamiment 007, Folder 4)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7210)
- Lewis-McChord Free Press Place of publication: Tacoma, Wash. Publisher: GI-Airmen Coalition, 1972-1973 (Box 163)
- Liberated Barracks Place of publication: Honolulu, Hawaii Publisher: Liberated Barracks Coffeehouse, 1971-1972 (Box 163)
- Liberator Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: W.L. Garrison & I. Knapp, 1855-1861 (Box 512)
  Researchers must use microfilm
- Liberty Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties, 1965-1972 (Box 219)
- Light Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Utility Union Workers of America, 1977-1996 (Box 223-224)
- The Link Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: United Community Centers, Inc., 1983-2008 (Box 225)
- Local 1-S News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Department Store Workers Union, 1978-2001 (Box 226-227)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7525)
- Local 3 Bakery Workers News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Bakery Confectionery and Tobacco Union, 1991-1996 (Box 228)
- Local 23-35 News / Blouse, Skirt and Sportswear Workers' Union, ILGWU, AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 23-25, 1971-1979 (Box 227)
- Local 100 Express: The Official Publication of TWU Local 100 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 100, Transport Workers Union of Greater New York, 2001-2009 (Box 69)
- Local 101 Marine Engineer Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Great Lakes District Local 101, MEBA, MTO, AFL-CIO, 1959-1960 (Box 228)
- Local 101 News Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Local 101, Utility Division, Transport Workers Union, 1962-1995 (Box 228)
- Local 342-50 Forefront Place of publication: Mineola, N.Y. Publisher: United Food and Commercial Workers Union, 1984-2001 (Box 227)
- Local One News: A Newspaper for Bakery Workers Place of publication:New York, N.Y. Publisher: Bakery & Confectionary Workers Int'l Union of America, Local No. 1, 1950-1955 (Box 228)
- Locomotive Engineer Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1973-1986 (Box 230-232)
- Log Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Seafarers International Union, Atlantic, Gulf, lakes and Inland Water Districts, AFL-CIO, 1980-1988 (Box 375-378)
- Long Lines Federation Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Federation of Long Lines Telephone Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 233)
- Los Angeles Free Press Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Art Kunkin, 1973-1974 (Box 233-234)
- Love and Rage Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Love and Rage, 1990-1991 (Box 28)
- The Machinist Place of publication: Upper Malboro, Md. Publisher: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1981-1993 (Box 235)
- Madison Tenant Union News Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: West Bronx Tenants Union, 1980-1980 (Box 236)
- El Malcriado Place of publication: Delano, Calif. Publisher: Farm Workers Organizing Committee, 1968-1983 (Box 238)
- Manna Place of publication: Fort Lauderdale, Fla., undated (Box 238)
- Marine Blues Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1969-1970 (Box 163)
- The Marxist-Leninist Vanguard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Workers' Communist Party, 1958-1976 (Box 238)
- Masses Place of publication: New York, NY Publisher: Masses Publishing Company, 1911-1917 (Box 507, Box 507A, Box 508, Box 508A, Box 508B, Box 509, Box 509A, Box 510, Box 511)
  Researchers must use reprint volumes or microfilm (Film R-7831).
- MESA Educator Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: National Administrative Committee, Mechanics Educational Society of America, 1973-1992 (Box 241-242)
- Morning Report Place of publication: Groton, Mass. Publisher: Fort Devens United Front, 1972 (Box 163)
- Moscow News Place of publication: Moscow, Russia Publisher: United Magazines and Newspapers, 1937 (Box 241)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7482)
- The Motorman, Conductor and Motorcoach Operator Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motorcoach Employees of America, 1937-1947 (Box 244)
- Mundo obrero Place of publication: Madrid, Spain Publisher: Partido Comunista de España, 2003-2006 (Box 244)
- Navy Times are Changin' Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Times Are Changin', 1972 (Box 163)
- New America: Publication of Social Democrats, U.S.A. Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Social Democrats, U.S.A., 1983-1985 (Box 237)
- New Directions for Women Place of publication: Dover, N.J. Publisher: New Directions for Women, 1975-1983 (Box 258)
- New Directions for Women in New Jersey Place of publication: Dover, N.J. Publisher: Coordinating Committee for Women's Rights Groups, 1972-1975 (Box 258)
- New Jersey Teamster News Place of publication: Jersey City, N.J. Publisher: New Jersey Teamsters Joint Council No. 73, 1967-2010 (Box 292A-292B)
- New Leader with Which Is Combined the American Appeal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New Leader Pub. Association, 1933 (Box 258)
- New Left Notes Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Students for a Democratic Society, 1969-1972 (Box 260)
- New Left Notes / SDS Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: SDS, 1966-1969 (Box 259)
- New Politics News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Convention Center, undated (Box 248)
- New Politics News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Conference for New Politics, 1967 (Box 261)
- New Solidarity Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: General Executive Bord [sic] of the Industrial Workers of the World, 1919 (Box 261)
- New Solidarity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1970-1987 (Box 261-275)
- New Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: C.P. Unit of the New York Times, 1936-1939 (Box 277)
- New Worker Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Communist Party of the United States of America (Marxist-Leninist), 1969 (Box 238)
- New York Alliance Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Labor Community for Change, 1980-1983 (Box 279)
- New York Brewery Worker Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Brewery Workers Local 3 & Local 46, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1970-1975 (Box 279)
- New York City Star Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hard Rain, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 101)
- New York Democratic Socialist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NY Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 238)
- New York Herald Tribune Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969-1970 (Box 279)
- The New York Longshoreman: Official Organ of the AFL International Longshoremen's Association Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: AFL International Longshoremen's Association, 1953-1954 (Box 281)
- New York Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Federation of Teachers, 1993-2012 (Box 286-286H)
- New York Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 2000-2010 (Box 287-287C)
- New York Teacher: Official Publication of New York State United Teachers Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 1972-2000 (Box 284-284L)
- New York Teacher. UFT Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 1978-1993 (Box 285-285D)
- New York Teacher News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Union of New York, 1943-1963 (Box 289)
- News: Not a Penny on the Rent Place of publication: Great Britain Publisher: United Tenants Action Committee, undated (Box 293)
- News & Letters Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: News & Letters, 1980-2007 (Box 295)
- News and Views Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, 1969-1983 (Box 293-294)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7033)
- News Service - American Postal Workers Union Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Postal Workers Union, 1975-2002 (Box 298-300)
- The Newsletter Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Newsletter, 1962-1969 (Box 297)
- Newsletter Place of publication: Waltham, Mass. Publisher: National Strike Information Center, 1970 (Box 293)
- The Next Step Place of publication: Heidelberg, Germany Publisher: S.C., 1970-1971 (Box 163)
- Nickel Review Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y. Publisher: Nickel Review, 1969-1971 (Box 296)
- Nitzotz = Nitsots Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Radical Zionist Alliance, 1973 (Box 296)
- Not the New York Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1978 (Box 512)
- Nuestra lucha Place of publication: Toledo, Ohio Publisher: Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 309)
- The NY Hackman Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1964-1965 (Box 279)
- NY Letter Carriers' Outlook Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Letter Carriers, Branch 36, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1983-2014 (Box 290-291)
- NYBC Update Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Building Congress, 2005-2008 (Box 277)
- NYSUT United Place of publication: Latham, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 2012-2014 (Box 293)
- NYU Inc. Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Inc., 2002-2004 (Box 260)
- Observer, 1970-1971 (Box 309)
- Occupied Wall Street Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Occupy Wall Street Media, 2011-2012 (Box 311)
- Occupied Wall Street Journal [Spanish ed.] Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Occupy Wall Street, 2011 (Box 311)
- Occupy! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: N+1, 2011 (Box 311)
- Off Our Backs Place of publication: Washington, D.C., 1970-1988 (Box 311-312)
- Office Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Office Workers Union, 1933-1935 (Box 313)
- The Olive Branch Place of publication: Jacksonville, Fla., 1972 (Box 164)
- Omega Press Place of publication: Koza, Japan Publisher: Omega House, 1972-1975 (Box 164)
- On Gogol Boulevard: Networking Bulletin for Activists Neither East nor West Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Neither East nor West, 1988-1990 (Box 313)
- On the Line Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America, 1969 (Box 313)
- On the Move Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1983-1984 (Box 313)
- Open City Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Caucus of Labor Committees in Coalition w/ Independent Student Groups, 1970 (Box 313)
- Open Ranks Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Baltimore GIs United, 1970 (Box 164)
- Opposition West Place of publication: Stanford, Calif. Publisher: Bay Area Coordinating Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 314)
- The Organizer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box 325)
- Out Now! Place of publication: Long Beach, Calif. Publisher: Movement for a Democratic Military, undated (Box 164)
- Painter's Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Painters' Free Press, 1961-1972 (Box 316)
- Palante Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Organización Obrera Revolucionaria Puertorriqueña, 1975-1976 (Box 318)
- Palante Place of publication: Havana, Cuba, 1972 (Box 318)